She woke up like this
Little is a comedy, fantasy, romance film directed by Tina Gordon.
Jordan Sanders, a take-no-prisoners tech mogul, wakes up one morning in the body
of her 13-year-old self right before a do-or-die presentation.
Her beleaguered assistant April is the only one in on the secret that her daily tormentor
is now trapped in an awkward tween body, just as everything is on the line.
Jordan Sanders, played by Regina Hall.
April Williams, played by Issa Rae.
Young Jordan Sanders, played by Marsai Martin.
Preston, played by Tone Bell.
Connor, played by Mikey Day.
Isaac, played by JD McCrary.
Little Women is a 2019 American coming-of-age period drama
film written and directed by Greta Gerwig.
It is the seventh film adaptation of the 1868 novel by Louisa May Alcott.
It chronicles the lives of the March sisters—Meg, Jo, Beth, and
Amy—in Concord, Massachusetts, during the 19th century.
It stars an ensemble cast consisting of Saoirse Ronan, Emma Watson (in her final film to date), Florence Pugh, Eliza Scanlen,
Laura Dern, Timothée Chalamet, Tracy Letts, Bob Odenkirk, James Norton, Louis Garrel, Chris Cooper, and Meryl Streep.
Sony Pictures initiated the development of the film in 2013, with Amy Pascal coming on board to
produce in 2015 and Gerwig hired to write its screenplay the following year.
Using Alcott's other writings as inspiration, Gerwig penned the script in 2018.
She was made director that same year, with the film
being the second she had solely directed.
Filming took place from October to December 2018 in the state of
Massachusetts, with editing commencing the day after filming wrapped.
Little Women premiered at the Museum of Modern Art in New York City on December 7, 2019, and was
released theatrically in the United States on December 25, 2019, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film received critical acclaim, with particular praise for Gerwig's screenplay and
direction as well as the performances of the cast, and grossed $218 million worldwide.
Among its numerous accolades, the film garnered six Academy Award nominations, including Best Picture, Best Actress (Ronan),
Best Supporting Actress (Pugh), Best Adapted Screenplay and Best Original Score, and won for Best Costume Design.
It also earned five British Academy Film Award nominations, with a win for
Best Costume Design, and two Golden Globe Award nominations.
The film explores themes of friendship, dreams,
business woman, bullying, personal assistant.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.